Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED DURING
THE FILMING OF THIS PRODUCTION
Father.
You may speak my daughter.
What’s wrong?
You seem like as if something is
bothering you.
Sing your heart out.
There is something you need to
know, father.
Father.
Dündar Bey!
Aygül Hatun.
There are important issues.
Excuse us.
What’s the matter, Alişar Bey?
Gündüz Bey and Dahi Bey are coming here.
As a Bannerlord, I'd like to
regulate things once again.
You demand what is rightfully yours.
I say...
...that we capture Gündüz now.
From here to Tent, go as the true Bey.
And settle down Kayı Tent once again.
Why not?
But…
...what are we going to about Osman?
Alişar Bey?
And also, what about Balgay?
If I settle down the Bey Tent...
...it's obvious how will Osman answer
to that.
Balgay is already hostile to us.
He can form an alliance with Osman.
We might have to fight with both of them.
If Osman and Balgay made an alliance...
...it means the apocalypse is already
here.
Don’t you dare to think it’s impossible
Alişar Bey.
I have seen so many incidents like
this in my life.
Then we will take them down together.
Geyhatu supports us.
He asks for Osman and Genghis' Laws
from us.
You just continue to stand as hard as
a rock.
Then..
...Gündüz will end up in a cage when he
arrives.
If needed, he may be free to give his
life.
He will understand what trying to replace
me stands for.
After him...
...we will decide what to do about
Osman and Balgay.
Alişar Bey!
My heart is lit with the fire of revenge.
May breathing be illicit to me before
I wreak their spite.
Illicit.
Where are the Laws, Osman?
So that we came to terms…
…and you agreed to die with me…
…you need to tell me where they are.
Why are these laws...
...very important for you?
When it comes to Genghis Khan…
…we can burn the whole world down, Osman.
Before him we were nothing but
pathetic people…
…then he made us become superior to
everybody.
We did not have a country before
he came into power.
Now all the world is ours.
You make a God out of Genghis.
The only thing you worship is fighting…
…and pillaging.
For now, maybe you are victorious.
However…
…you lack the soul to clench victory.
Souls are always with us.
Every single shaman give power to us.
What are you talking about?
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
''O Unbelievers...''
''…if you prayed for victory. Now has
the victory come to you..''
''If you desist from wrong…''
''…it will be the best for you.''
''If you return…''
''…so shall we.''
''Not the least good will your forces be
to you even if they were multiplied.
''Allah is with those who believe.''
You people do not understand.
Your land is ours now…
…as well as your palaces.
And those sons and daughters of you
have started to serve us.
You pay taxes every year.
Where is your God now?
Where is he?
Don’t let the time Allah spared for
tyrants...
...spoil you, Balgay.
The words that Pharaoh and Nimrod once
spoke are very similar to yours.
When Allah finally decides to punish you…
…you will not be guarded...
...neither by your soldiers...
...nor your Noyans.
Enough non sense!
Where are the Laws?
First, I need to be sure that you
are telling the truth.
Is my uncle with Alişar right now?
My birds told me so.
So far…
…they have never been wrong.
We will see.
Do you have water?
I will take ablution and do my prayers.
Then, we will be on our way.
It is not the time for your prayers.
Our enemies are waiting.
For us, nothing comes before praying.
You shall wait.
Put it there.
What is he doing?
He cleansed himself to worship.
How can you trust him, Commander Balgay?
Who said I trust him?
He betrayed me and sought to save his
Tent at the first opportunity.
We will wait for a while.
Be cautious.
Keep your ears and eyes wide open.
All preperations are over, Gündüz Bey.
We are ready for your commands.
I want everybody to be cautious, Ayaz.
We can’t predict what that Alişar Dog
will do.
Alps!
If we end up in an ambush...
...we will send all of them to hell!
As you command, my Bey!
How magnificent!
How magnificent my Valiants are.
Praise be!
How magnificent!
I see an army of steel.
As expected from my Gündüz Bey.
You once said reputation is more
important than swords, Bamsı Bey.
To bring the enemy to his knees...
...eventually one must use the power of
fear, you said.
We are trying our best...
...to follow and execute your words.
Praise be upon you, my Gündüz.
My Gündüz, I will be waiting for your
orders at the Tent.
For certain, Alişar will try to play
games on us.
In case of anything, I will organize the
rest for rioting against them.
We will create an army of children if
necessary.
After all, we are all born soldiers.
An army as a nation.
May Allah forbid Alişar and my uncle
make such mistakes.
With the name of Allah.
Are there any news from Osman, Bamsı Bey?
That I’m also hesitant about, my Gündüz.
It’s been too long.
Burhan?
Where is my Osman, Burhan?
Look at him!
We can cut his throat if we want to.
As if he is afraid of nothing.
Dying for his faith is what a Muslim
wants the most.
His faith is harder than a rock.
If we had even a bit of his faith…
…the whole world would be worshipping to
us by now.
My Allah.
Protect me from heathens.
There is no true deity except you.
You are the only one who has greatness.
You are the only ruler of seven skies and
the almighty throne.
I exonerate you from every physical
attributives.
Being thankful is only reserved to you.
You my Allah who rule all the realms.
My Allah...
...let my sword be sharp.
And protect my path.
Let us be victorious against all
tyrants, my Allah.
-Father!
-Husband?
Konur!
Göktuğ!
-Husband!?
-Father!?
Let’s be on our way already!
We lost time because of you.
Balgay!
Why are you in such hurry?
Walking on the same path with me has
a price.
You are already scared.
Wait.
We better go separately...
...as to hide our alliance.
Let’s go.
Go!
What are you up to, Boran?
What do you mean you left Osman alone
with Balgay’s soldiers?
Tell me!
What kind of an Alp are you?
How can you do this, Boran?
Osman Bey ordered me to do so.
We can’t question.
He ordered me to leave.
And now I am here.
Perhaps, my Bey already knows what is
best for him.
Alps!
We are not going to Alişar’s mansion.
Instead, we will search every corner
of the whole forest.
Don’t come back before you find my
brother.
As you command, my Bey!
Go now!
Gündüz Bey.
What?!
Our guest is very important.
Princess Adelfa, nephew of the
Byzantine Emperor.
Nephew of the emperor, huh?
Tell me more.
If Osman Bey didn’t forbid...
... she would have been married to
Geyhatu by now.
If the marriage happened...
... It would have been
many Oghuzs' nightmare.
This is the reason why Osman ordered
you to leave with the Princess...
...at the cost of his own life.
My Bey.
He ordered me to entrust the Princess
to you.
Keep her as a secret and don’t relieve
her identity.
My Allah protect Osman please.
Welcome to the Kayı Tent, Princess.
Aunt Selcan...
...take care of our guest.
But let nobody know about her existence.
I appreciate it.
I hope I will not disturb you.
You are our guest, my daughter.
You have place above our head.
Bala.
Come with us.
Follow me, my daughter.
Ohhh!
Ohh, Osman!
How could you risk your life like this?
Gündüz Bey.
If you allow me, I’d like to help
the other Alps with tracking.
There is a secret behind this, my Gündüz.
Something fishy, indeed.
What do you mean, Bamsı Bey?
My Gündüz.
Osman saved the girl
while Balgay was there.
So it means there will be no war.
But peace, my Gündüz.
Balgay will try to form an
alliance with my Osman.
Make your mind one with love, son.
So that these dark clouds over
the world of Islam scatter.
So that hopelessness comes to an end,
laziness comes to an end.
So the fire of ressurection is rekindled.
Eventually, my Sheikh.
Allow me to always use my mind and
heart for you, my Allah.
You will never stop, will you?
I won't, mother. You're not ashamed of
what you've done, but I am.
My father will eventually find out.
It's better if he hears it from me.
If you tell him and if he finds
out about Dündar Bey...
... you very well know what
will happen to me.
You're not thinking well, Aygül.
Tomorrow is uncertain.
Are you thinking well, mother?
It shows.
You always compared
my brother Batur to Osman.
You always blamed Osman
to make my brother shine out.
You pushed and pushed my father.
Then it wasn't enough and--
It wasn't enough.
It wasn't enough. You're right.
Your father couldn't handle it.
And as a mother, I did what was necessary.
Look. With the Mongol's orders...
... your father is talking to
the Banner Lord Alişar Bey...
... about how to hunt Osman down.
Are we any different?
My father is a Bey!
While he has to take care of
the whole tent...
... while there is chaos in the borders...
... it is his duty to
do what politics require.
What about you? Was it your duty?
My father is loyal to his tent
and his traditions.
You betrayed, mother.
The difference is your treachery.
If you think that way, my child, so be it.
A mother does everything to
protect her children.
But what can that mother do
if her child calls her a traitor?
I don't care about anything
outside my family.
I want you to be well.
Know this. If someone was to
hurt a single hair of yours...
... and if only the Mongols could
help me, I would ask them for help.
Instead of throwing you into the fire,
I'd rather burn myself.
I will stay quiet on one condition,
mother.
Tell my father yourself.
If he learns it from some one else,
it will be much worse for you.
Helen!
Where is Princess Sofia?
They said she wasn't in the castle.
He went to an important meeting.
As the castle's Commander,
why am I not aware of this?
Even though you promised, you couldn't
find out where Osman is, Salvador.
You better think about this first.
I know every place they go,
every whole they get into.
Our soldiers are tracking him everywhere.
Eventually--
Eventually, you'll find him. I'm sure.
Princess Sofia knows this as well.
Helen.
Alişar Bey must learn about these facts
as well.
Okay.
That's Master Yannis' spy.
If he's here, there
must be important developments.
Osman.
He's back.
With Balgay.
They united against Princess Sofia.
That's impossible.
Osman will never--
Salvador...
You still don't now who Osman is.
And you say that you'll find him.
I hope Osman doesn't get in trouble
because of a Byzantinian lady.
Bala? My daughter, are you jealous?
No, Selcan mother.
I'm worried about Osman.
While we're on the topic, here's a
couple of advice from mother Selcan.
They shall be a lesson to you.
My Osman is a known Valiant.
A mad valiant.
A handsome one at that.
There will be lots of women
who want to be his wife.
You need to prepare for that.
Praise be!
Does it look good?
You're outstanding, my Princess daughter.
We should settle you down here.
We have lots of Valiant Alps
next to Osman Bey.
We'll espouse you with one of them.
They can't give you palaces like Geyhatu.
But they will make their
home a palace for you.
I'd rather go to hell than go
through that other marriage.
This place is heaven next
to that, believe me.
Come on.
Tell me. How did these things happen?
Messengers have been coming to
Constantinople for months.
Geyhatu finally convinced the Emperor to
marry him through letters and gifts.
I didn't want to.
I prayed a lot. I begged that
this marriage didn't happen.
Thankfully, Jesus almighty heard my voice.
He sent Osman Bey.
Geyhatu's plans were
hindered by Osman, thankfully.
Who knows what other troubles
these Mongols would have caused us.
Osman Bey is a real hero
He saved me from those tyrants.
You should have seen that moment!
He risked his life for me.
A real hero.
May Jesus Christ protect him.
Mother Mary forbid if something happens
to Osman Bey, I can't forgive myself.
My daughter!
I have to take care of something.
Take care of the Princess.
Don't you worry, Selcan mother.
Okay then.
It seems that what Balgay has done
troubled Geyhatu.
He wants to regulate the lands.
He wants to do it with you.
The fact that he shared
his plans with you...
... shows that you're still
in charge, Alişar Bey.
I am no more, Dündar Bey.
It's us from now on.
We're already connected by spirit.
No one can destroy our alliance
once we're connected by blood as well.
We'll start with Kayı Tent.
Once we take your throne back.
We won't go far with just words,
Alişar Bey.
A bloody fight awaits us.
I can't rest before I take
my son's revenge!
I can't sleep.
I have to take my Batur's revenge.
Once you take the throne back and become
both the Kayı's bey and the land's Bey...
... the rest is easy.
Those who killed my son-in-law
will regret what they have done.
There will be people who don't
want me to get back on the throne.
There will be lots of noise.
Why do we feed all these soldiers?
Why do we host Geyhatu's soldiers?
If they can't do their jobs
when the time comes...
... why do we keep all these
dogs tied up in here?
We'll besiege the Tent.
Then we'll get them!
Those who are connected to you will not
be just watching I suppose.
We'll drown them in the blood
they spilt, Dündar Bey!
The Mongols won't let go
of this, Bala Hatun.
You're in danger because of me.
Not because of you, Princess.
The Mongols have been
bothering us for a long time.
We've been dealing with them
for a long time.
How will it be from now on? What will
the emperor say when he finds out?
What if something worse
happens to Osman Bey?
If something happens to Osman Bey...
... this Tent and many others
will rise, Princess.
Don't you worry.
Osman Bey saved many Hatuns like you.
What's the reason for
your unexpected visit?
Where's my uncle, Alişar Bey?
As we know, Dündar Bey is dead.
If he's alive, he's not here
as you can see.
Alişar...
Take Dündar out of the hole you
put him in.
Or I'll throw both of you in
bottomless wells.
You're talking to the Banner Lord
Geyhatu assigned.
Watch your words, Balgay!
Or I'll cut your tongue off!
When did you become so brave?
Huh?
As I see, two enemies have
united against me.
I didn't know that I scared you this much.
Cut it short, Alişar!
Where is my uncle?
Everyone is talking about
how you killed your uncle.
He's probably where you buried him!
Alişar...
You're wrong if you think you're the boss
just because you have someone's word.
I don't care about your Bannerlordship!
I'll ask one last time.
Where is Dündar Bey?
He's probably where you buried him!
Balgay. Are you lying?
Or is he lying?
Kongar!
Search the palace.
What is it, Alişar?
You've become dense like a bow.
What is it that you hide?
I'm not the one who
is supposed to become dense.
It's you.
You're searching the palace of the Banner
Lord assigned by Geyhatu.
Aren't you afraid? On top of that,
with a rebel who killed the Kayı's Bey.
Kayı's Bey is my father.
My brother is his deputy.
The real rebel is my uncle
who you're hiding!
How will you deal with this, Alişar?
I'm the Banner Lord.
The Bey is who I declare.
We choose our Beys with Oghuz tradition.
Not words!
My brother gets his power from this.
Where do you get your power, Alişar?
You killed Batur.
Dündar is lost.
What kind of a tradition is this,
Osman Bey?
We neither killed Batur
nor did we betrayed our uncle.
The roads lead to you, Alişar.
When I bring this trick to the light...
You'll look for a hole to hide in!
Everything that comes to Kayı Tribe is
because of your arrogance, Osman.
You can't teach me!
It's over.
You can't escape now.
There is nobody in the mansion.
Who is fool now, huh?
So, someone is lying.
Eeeh, your alliance is over now.
- Do you know why I don't kill you?
- Why?
Because nobody should see that Osman
Bey kills a Muslim in front of Mongols.
However, the next time we face each other,
I will take your head off your chest.
Then, they will witness a Munafiq's
(factious) death.
Are you trying to fool me with your
little brain?
Don't let me see you again, or
I will crush you.
Your information is not true, Balgay.
You told me that my uncle is with Alişar.
- We both know he is lying.
- A good commander has good spies.
If your spies fool you, that means
the Mongol army's situation is awful.
Still, I will keep my promise.
You wish to learn who has the laws of
Genghiz Khan.
Let me tell you.
I gave them to Yannis.
What are you looking for is in
Kulucahisar Castle.
You are setting me against my fellows.
You say you've had many wars, but you still
can't distinguish between friend and enemy
Yannis wanted Genghis Khan's laws
in return of your life.
Now you can take care of him.
Kongar, get ready. You'll turn
Kulucahisar Castle into a grave.
You need to bring me what belongs
to me.
Or I will take your life.
Yes, Commander Balgay.
Where will you go?
I will confront those who degraded me
in front of Osman Bey.
Osman Bey, they wait for you.
I will arrive.
Mother, why are we returning to the tribe?
Don't you know what is going to happen?
I know, of course, but this is
what your father wants.
You can't escape from what you have done,
my Aygül.
- Father...
- My Bey, are you okay?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
I suffer from both an arrow wound and
ulcer.
But, I am fine now, don't worry.
Dündar Bey, do you want to give a break?
Saltug, son, gather wood, we'll set fire.
We may get cold.
My Bey...
I have something to tell you.
What's now, Hatun?
Tell me.
Hatun, tell me!
What is your problem?
If you are worried about the tribe,
don't.
We are not guilty.
You are not, but...
I am terrified by what I've done, my Bey.
You should know that first.
I regret disobeying you.
Zöhre, don't push me.
Say what you are going to say?
What have you done, ha?
I've gone to Balgay.
Do you hear what you are saying, Hatun?
My Batur went after Osman
and you rejected him...
I had no choice...
- Father, father don't.
- Go away, let go of me!
Tell me!
Tell me what you have done!
While my Batur was going after Osman...
I didn't want him to be slaughtered
by Mongols.
I went to Balgay and offered Osman
in return of Batur.
I didn't want my son to be hurt.
What else do you have?!
Then Balgay strangled me to find out
who informed Geyhatu.
Your real problem, my Bey, is that I said
it was Gündüz Bey.
Father! I beg you, don't!
- Get out of my way, Aygül!
What have you done to me, Zöhre?
What troubles have you caused me?
How can you crush me like this?
Take your hands off!
Don't you touch me!
I was feeding a snake all these years!
Pity!
What a shame!
I have a child more precious than my life.
I'm not killing you for her sake.
But...
... if I see you do one more thing wrong,
I won't listen to her and I'll kill you.
Remember this.
This sword I stuck into the dirt...
... will pierce your heart.
It will be your end.
Isn't it hard living in a Tent,
Bala Hatun?
Don't you get cold in winter?
Don't these tents break down in rain?
They are warm in winter, and cool in
summer. Not one drop of rain can get in.
We call them haircloth tents. Made from
felt. They are durable.
Do servants and Masters live in
different tents?
How do you decide?
Servants?
Princess... We don't have masters.
We are all equal. We don't have
any servants or masters.
How can that be? Who does your footwork?
Everyone does their own work. Our beliefs
don't allow us to have slaves, Princess.
In Islam, we only serve Allah.
Hatuns and men have different duties.
Everyone does what they do the best.
What about your King?
Is Osman Bey your King?
Beys manage our Tent.
Kayı Tent's Bey is Osman Bey's brother
Gündüz Bey.
Everything is different.
Very different.
Thank Jesus Christ he sent Osman Bey
and you for me.
I will pray for all of you.
Go inside the tent. Stay inside, Princess.
What is going on, Bala Hatun?
- What are you going to do?
- Get inside the tent. Relax.
I'll see who's coming.
- Welcome Dündar Bey!
- Welcome, my Bey!
Welcome, Dündar Bey.
Welcome, my Bey.
My Allah! May my Allah don't keep anyone
away from their homeland!
May my Allah, who allowed me to return,
allow me to take my revenge.
Amin, father. Amin.
Welcome, my Bey.
Uncle!
How can you return to this Tent?
How can you stand before me?
You got up on my throne right after
I died, and you're calling me out.
We know that you're working with Alişar.
Alps saw you with Alişar at Batur's funeral.
Don't you lie no more and
make a fool out of yourself!
Thanks to Alişar Bey, I found
my son's killers.
What did you do? Huh?
What did you do?
You attacked my daughter and my woman!
If you tracked the infidels instead...
... I wouldn't need to work
with Alişar Bey!
What are you talking about, uncle?
Who are Batur's killers?
How did you find out?
Are you asking this question now?
You left me alone with my pain.
With Alişar, we found the Mongol
soldiers who killed my Batur.
I took my son's revenge with these hands.
What did you do? Huh?
What?
Wait, uncle? Breathe.
Let's talk about this calmly.
I'll say what you did.
You sent my daughter and wife to
Alişar Bey's palace for nothing!
It wasn't enough. You tried to kill me.
We're all here.
If it wasn't enough, kill us.
We sent Zöhre Hatun and Aygül to Alişar's
palace for a reason!
I know. I'm aware of everything.
But before we blame someone...
... we listen to them, as it's our
tradition. We don't hurt anyone...
... before listening to their reasons.
Zöhre Hatun did everything to
look for solutions.
Not for throwing our Tent into the fire.
If someone's going to call people out,
it's me.
Of course, there are questions to be
asked, answers to be given.
Everything has a time.
From now on, Dündar Bey will make
everyone pay for what they have done.
Know that.
What is it, Melik?
Your eyes are cloudy.
Can we trust Dündar Bey, my Bey?
What if he is playing with us?
When you're feeding a lamb,
you cut its wool.
You wash it and cut again.
First time, the animal gets scared.
Then it gets used to it.
When you're going to kill it, it thinks
that its wool will be cut again.
But the knife is on its neck
this time, not on its wool.
For now, we'll...
... cut Dündar's wool.
So that he doesn't scare when
I put a knife on his throat.
As long as he has such greed and grudge,
he'll always serve us.
Zorba.
Yes, my Bey.
Take this letter to Konya
right now.
Be on the alert.
Protect this letter at the cost of
your life.
The order is order, my bey.
Balgay.
Now, let him know he has
the power.
We'll see what he will do when
Geyhatu learns everything.
What do you think he'll do, my bey?
He'll butter up and apologize to you.
I will make Balgay dance like a dancer boy
in these lands.
Come on!
Fortunately, I found you, my bey.
You didn't because I wasn't lost, Boran.
I took the princess to them safely,
bey.
Thank you.
I got some things to do.
Alişar and my uncle do something
behind me.
I will not show up until I solve it.
Inform Bala Hatun.
I'm waiting for her.
She knows where I'll be waiting.
But take some soldiers on Konya road to
lay an ambush.
We need to know what he's talking with Konya
in order to know what Alişar is thinking.
What if we learn?
If you have information, you come.
I'll do your order with great pleasure.
Welcome, Dündar Bey.
We become peaceful thanks to you.
May you live long.
I will never forget your loyalty.
When will we destroy their Tent, my bey?
I came here for one reason.
First, let's solve it.
Then, I will kill all of them.
Alişar Bey.
I have some important news for you.
Osman is working with Balgay.
Understood.
Why this misbeliever is in your
mansion, Alişar Bey?
It is the duty of bannerlord to control
here, Dündar Bey.
Helen, who the princess Sofia sent,
brought some important news.
The princess who has been sent to
marry with Geyhatu has disappeared.
I think Osman is the reason for this.
It didn't finish.
Your nephew is coming here.
With Balgay who he is working with.
Didn't I tell you, Alişar Bey?
I saw a lot of things with these eyes.
I'll wait for them.
But, they shouldn't see you here,
Dündar Bey.
From now on, your duty is Tent.
If the princess is in the Tent, wouldn't taking
her to Geyhatu make you more powerful?
Also, Geyhatu will give whatever we want.
All Mongol golds will be ours.
We'll get rid of Osman and Balgay.
You will be docile in the Tent in order to
save the princess, Dündar Bey.
You will hold your grudge for some time.
What about?
I would eat their raw livers in order to
take my revenge.
Raw liver.
Your first wife and son are on the road,
my bey.
Thank you.
When my braveman comes here, we'll
be more powerful, I hope.
Now...
Listen to me carefully.
There is a Byzantine woman taken
into Tent secretly.
Byzantine woman?
Nobody said us.
They took a precaution.
But you'll find.
What are we gonna do?
Kill her?
We'll kidnap her.
Trace and follow.
Don't feel sorry for her.
But never get caught.
Got it.
Thank you.
Thank you, my bey.
Go.
You sent for me.
What's happening, Helen?
Who is coming?
An important guest of ours.
Here.
He has come.
Commander Kongar.
Welcome.
We would like to be prepared for you.
But there was no time.
Where is Princess Sofia?
Not in castle.
She wanted me to take care of you.
You're either dumb or you trust your God
so much.
If I want, I can destroy this castle.
But there isn't even one soldier of you
on your ramparts.
Do you defend your castle like this?
If we saw you as an enemy, destroying
such an enemy wouldn't even be a pleasure.
My soldiers protect us just from Turks,
commander Kongar.
They can't protect us from such a great
commander.
Shut up!
As you know I was gonna come here, you
know for what I came.
Of course, I know.
But first come in if you like.
I'll prepare a room for you and take
a rest.
Don't mess with me.
Give what belongs to Balgay.
You give it with your own hands so that
my soldiers don't destroy your soldiers...
...with their strong fists.
Don't waste my time.
I don't have any time to wait.
Come on!
Ayaz.
He said whoever go to Konya, stop them.
I hope we won't go back without
doing anything, brother.
Osman is struggling to be
an Alp for a long time.
Do you hear what're you saying,
Dumrul brother.
Many Valiants in Oghuz want to clash
side by side with Osman Bey.
Here, infidels are coming.
Long live with your intelligence,
Osman Bey.
What do you think you are doing, panders?
Get down!
Or I'll kill you.
Or I'll kill you without hesitating.
Salamun Alaikum.
Assalamualaikum.
May Allah bless you with
plentifulness, Osman.
Here you are.
When the princess was kidnapped, Geyhatu
went crazy in his palace.
The Byzantine Ruler who relies on Moghol
went crazy.
We defeated them.
May you live long.
May you live long, too.
Balgay confronted me. He
wanted to kidnap the princess.
He wants to take back his lost
reputation.
Even if we lose everything, we should
protect our soul and reputation always.
Well, how do we lose our reputation?
Human being, in this mortal life, struggles
to death in order to not lose the reputation.
But, being ungratefulness and thanklesness
they lose their reputation towards Allah.
Because our Allah's mercy is greater than
his rage, we survive after all.
But, there isn't anything worse than losing
the reputation of a government, son.
Well. How does a government lose
reputation?
If the morals of the society which make the
government a government get out of order...
...it means the reputation has
started to be lost.
How do we understand that?
If scholars start to lose their
nobility...
If there is injustice...
If there isn't any respect to mother
and father and families break down...
If there isn't any love between couples...
If divorcing is increasing and there
isn't any demand for the knowledge...
If no one cares about intelligence...
If the believers don't live
like they believe...
It means the government is losing
its reputation.
In such a case, what the leader of
society should do?
Leaders are like a reflection
of society.
The society sees them like themselves.
So, the leader himself should be moral.
Everybody should know him as a guide.
They should try to be like him
and live like him.
Our deceased prophet, he turned
stone-hearted people into merciful people.
He took out the water of mercy from
the desert that...
...will help people to solve
their problems.
Now, there's a new duty.
We'll take the road to spoil new
plans.
The expedition is ours and the victory is
Allah's.
I'm listening to you.
Sofia knows that very well
in this chest...
...there is an assurance of heaven
for Balgay.
No!
I hope Balgay won't sell us out to Osman
for the strong sovereign he'll have...
...thanks to those laws.
Commander Kongar.
Also, If I were you...
...I wouldn't trust anything that
Osman has a relationship.
You talk it with Balgay when he comes.
Just for those worthless laws...
The lands that you turn into a bloodbath
will be your end.
Margarit Monastery is planning
something new.
Who are they?
The monks who are determined to
kill all Turks in Bithynia region.
Now, they're planning something new.
By agreeing with Geyhatu...
...they want to ascend someone
else to Byzantium throne.
I need you to find who he is.
We should punish them
heavily.
It won't be that easy to infiltrate
between them.
I need to make preparation.
We'll tell you the necessary information.
The things you've to do is
in this bag.
Examine it
You'll not be alone in this historical
duty.
Who will be my fellow?
A kayı son like you will
be with you.
He'll find you.
Come on.
Good luck.
My Allah...
Please speed this fearless braveman who
takes part in this difficult duty.
His name may be a great mountain
that brutal ones can't conquer.
His sword may cut the infidel cities
like a silk fabric.
But his sword may also be a soul for those
brave men who don't fear from death...
...and open a period.
Amin.
I miss having a conversation with
you, my sister.
Thanks to who make us come together.
Since you've gone...
...Tent is like it's theirs.
We're like foreign among them.
They found the opportunity to do it.
Let it boil.
- Bala Hatun spends a lot of time here.
- Yes.
She's so afraid that she may remain
separate from Osman.
She's always with Selcan Hatun.
- Great job, Hatun. It's beautiful.
- Thank you, Selcan Hatun.
It will tinge its color.
They never stop.
They're full of mischief.
Welcome, Zöhre Hatun.
Zöhre Hatun...
Please don't leave us to
their hands again.
They think they're the owner of the tent.
They're being obstinate.
They brought a new girl to the tent.
Girl?
- Who? Why did she come?
- I don't know.
They protect her.
Bala and Selcan Hatun take care of her.
We'll see about it.
We'll bend their necks.
Look at Bala Hatun.
She thinks she's the wife of
Osman. Look at her.
She's so big-headed.
We'll take care of them.
But I need your help.
- We shouldn't do anything that will turn heads to us.
- We should.
But not to us.
We'll burn those.
Now...
We'll take care of their guest.
So that the girl is taken care
of Selcan Hatun and Bala...
then they should lose her.
If the girl is important for
them, it is for Osman too.
Aygül, don't worry daughter.
I won't do anything without
your father's consent.
Come on.
Allah knows what you're talking about.
You have your eyes on me
all the time, Selcan Hatun.
You look with an evil eye.
Do you refrain from me?
But that's enough. Deal
with your own business.
I keep an eye on the betrayers.
You know.
Don't affect these girls.
I have my eyes on you.
Don't do anything foolish from now on.
Stop.
Don't say anything.
I won't forgive you if I
see your mistake again.
They're doing this all the time.
If we stop, they'll keep doing it.
We should do what's necessary.
They shouldn't harm us anymore.
Tell us. What do you have in your mind?
Burçin will take care of this job.
My Karayel.
We survived many hardships with you.
Many enemies bend their knees.
They're so angry now.
They're waiting for us to fall so
that they will try to kill us.
That's why we have to be
alive all the time.
And awake.
My Karayel. My loyal comrade.
Karayel.
It's time to marry, I guess.
Sheikh Edebalı was on retiring.
I'm saying that, I
should ask for Bala Hatun.
What do you think?
Mashaallah.
What if he doesn't give
her to me, Karayel?
Then I swear I'll abduct Bala.
Huh?
What if...
Bala doesn't want to marry me?
Mashaallah.
My dearest is coming!
- Good riddance, Osman Bey.
- It is.
It is.
It's hyacinth, sir.
It charms the brave.
It's light. I want something more intense.
Of course, my Bey.
White musk. It comes from Arabic lands.
- You're doing your job well.
- Thanks, my Bey.
Always be in my palace.
Your command, my Bey.
My Bey.
Zorba.
What happened to Zorba?
Have you lost your tongue? Talk!
Talk!
Soldiers in the frontier area...
They found Zorba's horse.
They killed the carrier.
Zorba... He's not around.
Do you know what happens
if Zorba is caught by Osman? Huh?!
All of our work will be spoiled.
Osman or Balgay abducted Zorba!
Balgay is after Genghis Khans's laws.
Osman did it.
Inform Dündar Bey immediately.
If Zorba is brought to the tent...
he show no mercy.
He should kill him.
A single mistake will devastate all of us.
Come on. Come on!
Your command, my Bey.
It's good to see you smiling.
Why are you that happy?
My steps are going well.
Everything I do is going well, my Bala.
Why wouldn't I smile?
It's good for you to save the princess.
She's liked our tent. She may
not want to go.
If she wants to stay, our doors are open.
We have our tent, place
and bread to share.
She's the niece of the
Imperial of Byzantine.
She has a big power behind her.
But you know better than me.
I know many things about her. I
inquired about her.
Princess Adelfa is so important, Bala.
So important.
If she's so important, don't
worry Osman Bey.
I'll protect her at the cost of my life.
Princess is important.
But...
if she didn't exist, how could I know
about my woman's concern?
How could I know about your...
love's pettishness?
Bala...
Don't you know that I'll ruin this whole world...
for your tears?
Huh? Don't you know, my Bala?
Why do you upset yourself?
Don't.
Your place in my heart is
getting bigger every day.
The fire of your love burns me every day.
I couldn't...
When love is in the heart...
I lose my mind, Osman.
As long as you love me, I'll never let
anyone harm you.
I'll never let anyone harm you...
Don't worry.
You're destined to me, my Bala.
I'm so thankful to Allah for it.
Osman.
Dündar Bey came to the tent.
Once Alişar Bey took Zöhre
and Aygül to his palace.
Now they're all back.
Dündar Bey said that he found
Batur's killer.
He's said that he'll obey
Gündüz, if necessary.
Alişar and Dündar...
What are they up to again?
Can I come, my Bey?
Come, Boran.
I have important news, my Bey.
My Bey.
What, Saltuk?
I have some news from Alişar Bey.
He thinks that Zorba is abducted
by Osman.
He's told us to trace
Zorba and kill him...
or else, all our plans are ruined.
Oh my Allah. Now we
have to deal with this.
Osman isn't around.
If they have caught Zorba, they
will question him.
Follow one of Osman's Alps.
Trace him.
- If you find...
- Kill him?
Come on.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim. (in the name of Allah, the merciful and compassionate.)
Do you know what ant means, my Akça?
I don't know, my Sheikh.
It's not just an ant if you
know how to look.
It's the verse of the Book of Nature
(Quran) if you know how to read.
It's the sign of
hard work, perseverance and...
collaboration.
Ants are weak when they're alone.
However...
they show how powerful they
are when they're together.
How can we see, my Sheikh?
What should we do to see?
You should see water drops
as a guide, Zulfiqar.
As a water drop, you're alone.
You only vaporize and you disappear.
But...
If you go somewhere else...
you'll be home to the fishes...
and you'll be water for the dry fields.
You learn that union is strength.
Your inability will be your power.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
Allah gives us a mystery in
Neml Surah (ant Surah).
Prophet Sulaiman goes on a voyage...
with his army.
The army respects the ant law and stop.
Why?
Because what makes Prophet
Sulaiman's state big is...
not that he rules the world.
It's because even when he rules
the world, he sees the ant law.
How can we see that law?
Prophet Sulaiman...
was the biggest sultan in the world.
He owned a big land.
Muslims couldn't find the poor
to help them.
They were very skillful when
using weapons.
His army scared cruel ones...
and became a hope to everyone.
To learn about this improvement...
many rulers visited Prophet Sulaiman.
Belkıs was one of them.
Visitors were surprised by what they saw.
Because the moral improvement...
was prominent.
People's love of the afterlife...
...were a lot greater than their love
of life.
When the time of prayer called...
...people would run to pray...
...instead of eating. So they could
thank the one who gave it to them.
May Allah grant the awakening from
the sleep of blindness...
...to the ummah of Muhammad.
-Amin, my Sheikh.
-Inshallah.
Will we be able to live up to see these
days, my Sheikh?
Will we be freed from this press?
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
Muslims left the compass of science...
...morals are corrupted...
...the values that defined us
had been destroyed.
With the guidance of oracles...
...if we can be a Suleiman, Zulkarneyn,
Joseph and David of our time...
...why not, Akça?
Our good Allah didn't tell us these
parables just as stories...
...but for us to take them as our
cause...
...and take the mentioned people
us our guide.
If we hold Allah's bond strongly...
...for sure, Allah is the one who
keeps promises.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
My Bey, we hunted Alişar's runner
on his way to Konya.
And we found this on him.
Thank you, Boran.
What does it say, Osman Bey?
Alişar tells Geyhatu that the princess
is seized by us...
...invited him here, with his army.
He says, I'm responsible for the unrest
and Balgay is responsible for helping me.
And that we are rebels on revolt.
Now I understand why my uncle came
to the tents out of the blue.
He will kidnap the princess.
-What will we do?
-I have an important job.
Now listen to me carefully.
You'll stop Dündar Bey from
abducting the princess.
We should lead my uncle to a trap.
Interrogate Alişar's man.
Do it away from the tents,
if possible.
Alişar will do anything he can to take
his man back.
And you'll breath down on their necks.
Is it clear?
Yes, my Bey.
This arrival of Dündar...
...it doesn't seem good.
Only Allah knows whether it's good
or bad.
What was I supposed to do,
Bamsı Bey? Huh?
Was I supposed to send my uncle to
Alişar's mansion?
Thank you, son. Thank you.
But when the thief is inside,
a lock is useless.
We got Zorba, my Bey.
He waits outside the tents.
Let's go and find his tongue,
Bamsı Bey.
Let's see what is he hiding.
Yes, let us do that.
What's up my nephew?
What's this hurry?
Where are you going?
The goods that will go to Yenipazar
are lacking. A caravan is coming.
I'm going to check them, uncle.
Thank you, thank you.
Yenipazar is important for us.
The goods that will be sold in there
are important for our tents.
I always say it, when there is no coin...
...there is no ruling.
You understand it the best in these tents.
When you sit on the Bey's throne,
we'll see it closely.
And another thing I see is your support
for me...
...despite resentments and ailments,
I can't forget that, my nephew.
Law stands with power but walks
with experience.
I see that you are very diligent...
If there is a task that your uncle can do,
say it freely.
And my brother, too, would want to see
us like this; shoulder to shoulder.
Dündar Bey separated the white from
the black.
Now we should blend both the white
and the black to the red of blood.
Welcome.
When I heard that we have a guest,
I wanted to bring a sherbet and a welcome.
This is our indigenous sherbet.
We treat it to every newcomer.
What a lovely smell. What is that
made of?
We call it cranberry.
Drink it, sister. Let's see if you'll
like it.
Don't even try, Zorba.
You can't go anywhere before speaking.
Do you know what you are doing?
I'm the helper of the bannerlord!
Alişar Bey will turn this place into
a bloodbath!
Enough!
You should think of my Osman Bey's fury!
You'll soon see what fury is.
Lower that thing, Saltuğ.
C'mon.
The hunter became the hunted.
Cut a long story short, there is no need
for pointless bickering, my nephew.
It seems, one calamity is a better teacher
than a thousand counsel.
I thought about it. What happened
caused me a son.
When we lost Aybars, I couldn't control
Bamsı Bey.
Now, I understand him better.
But we farewelled Aybars with farewells...
...by saying Allahu Akbar. That was
appropriate for the valiant of Kayı.
But I farewelled my son...
...my Batur...
...all alone.
It's like there is a furnace burning
right in here.
It's like, even if this river wouldn't be
enough to put the fire off.
If you think there is a mistake in
my doings...
...forgive me because of my pain,
my nephew.
But after all, there can't be two heads...
...on a single body.
Our laws choose you as our Bey.
And we should follow you.
Not at all, uncle.
Not at all.
Have you followed me?
Untie me and I'll tell you.
Ayaz, calm down, brother.
Calm down!
-We need them alive.
-Yes. Yes, we do.
But since both of them are here,
they must've known of each other.
Thank Allah that you are helper
of my Dündar Bey.
Otherwise, I would kill you right away.
He can't come here before getting
Dündar Bey's approval.
There is something behind this, brother.
I know there is.
Hang on, warriors!
Arrows coming this way!
There are too many trees, we should
go on foot.
Ayaz, you stay with them.
Look, I've brought you food.
Princess?
Selcan Hatun!
What's up my girl?
What's wrong?
Missing. Adefa is missing,
Selcan Hatun.
Her tent is empty. I couldn't
find her nearby either.
What are you saying, Bala?
Osman Bey summoned me. I went
to meet him.
He told me that Dündar Bey and his
supporters will try to kidnap Adefa.
He told me to be cautious.
I went to Adefa as soon as I came back.
But I was too late, Selcan Hatun.
We are too late.
Dündar... You did it again.
Day that your doings will be exposed,
you and your followers...
...you will all come to an end.
Kongar, you'll stay here.
Do you think that it is too much for me
to carry the laws of Genghis Khan?
I'll give another task, at least as
honorable as that one.
What is it?
You will watch Osman closely.
A friend of us who is an enemy in truth.
You'll watch his every step.
Not only the spirits on the ground
and the sky...
...there are some others who protect him.
We need to find the track of this
power.
Yes, Commander Balgay.
When I return, Osman will
either obey us...
...or to his death.
You won't be alone in this
historical task...
...a son of Kayı who carries the same
blood with you...
...will be with you.
He'll find you.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com